http://www.snapstream.com/privacy

Request Pricing Request PricingLoginFeaturesOverviewProduct TourRecord & Search TVClip & ShareStreams & EventsMoco: Monitoring & ComplianceHow it WorksHow it WorksRecord & Search TVShare TV Clips to Twitter & FacebookDistribute TV & VideoMonitoring & Compliance NEWLive Video ProductionProductsSnapStream ProSnapStream EnterpriseSnapStream CloudEncoder (Component & HDMI)Encoder (QAM & ATSC)Encoder (HD-SDI)Encoder (DVB-T)Proxy Generation Node NEWSnapStream TVStorage CalculatorIndustriesNews & MediaEntertainmentUniversitiesSportsGovernmentCustomersCase StudiesTV SearchClip & ShareMonitoringSupportPricingTrainingCompanyAbout UsCareersBlogPressContact UsLoginThank you! Your submission has been received!Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the formThank you! Your submission has been received!Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the formHow it WorksHow it WorksRecord & Search TVShare TV Clips to Twitter & FacebookDistribute TV & VideoMonitoring & Compliance NEWLive Video ProductionSnapStream ProSnapStream EnterpriseSnapStream CloudEncoder (Component & HDMI)Encoder (QAM & ATSC)Encoder (HD-SDI)Encoder (DVB-T)Proxy Generation Node NEWSnapStream TVStorage CalculatorOverviewProduct TourRecord & Search TVClip & ShareStreams & EventsMoco: Monitoring & ComplianceTV SearchClip & ShareMonitoringIndustriesNews & MediaEntertainmentUniversitiesSportsGovernmentCustomersCase StudiesSupportSupportEmail SnapStream SupportVolicon Support Home Page NEWEmail Volicon Support NEWVolicon Knowledgebase NEWVolicon Manuals NEWVolicon Transition Center NEWTrainingRelease NotesTraining NEWUser ResourcesAdmin ResourcesHow-To GuidesStorage CalculatorSupport PoliciesStatusEDU TrainingCheat SheetsQuick Start GuidesKnowledgebaseSearch SupportCompanyAbout UsCareersCustomersBlogPressContact UsLoginRequest PricingLoginRequest Pricing Thank you! Your submission has been received!Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the formPrivacy PolicySnapStream is Committed to Your Online SecurityOnline privacy is a serious concern. At SnapStream, we uphold the same level of privacy standards that we demand from other websites.We will never sell, trade, or otherwise make available any personally identifiable information to any 3rd party organization or company not affiliated with SnapStream.What information do we collect?We collect information such as name, e-mail, mailing address, and/or phone number from you when you respond to a survey or fill out a form.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:(a) Traffic Analysis - SnapStream uses software programs to analyze traffic to this website. These programs collect aggregate data, not personal information, and are critical to improving the user experience within the website.(b) Periodic Emails - The email address you provide may be used to send you occasional information such as company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. We will never sell or share your information with anyone else not affiliated with SnapStream. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.(c) Customer Service - Where applicable, your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.(d) Forms - Inquiry forms, such as information requests or site registration, collect information that is securely stored and will only be used to direct you to the resources you seek. This may include follow up by one of our associates to answer questions you may have.Links to Other SitesThe SnapStream website may contain links to other website and internet resources. SnapStream is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other website and internet resources.Do we use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.Questions and ConcernsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at marketing@snapstream.com.Last Update: 2/17/2017
